barcelonaconnect.com 2013-11-25

# Privacy Policy

****Privacy Policy****

**Information We Collect**  
Go and Connect is a network of websites that correspond to different cities and services worldwide. For full access to our services, you will need to register and create a User Profile by using our online registration form, where you will be required to provide us with your contact information (e.g. e-mail address) and some other information relating to your identity, such as name, date of birth, country of origin etc. Every user can select whether they wants certain data to be available to other network users, such as their email address or date of birth. This information is then made available to other signed-in users within the Go and Connect network. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under 18 years of age) do not submit any personal information to us. In addition, we use cookies on certain pages of our site. Cookies are stored on your hard drive when using the Go and Connect website to allow the user to interact correctly with the website. They may also be used for statistical purposes and to send you new information about any of the Go and Connect websites. If you don’t want to receive new information or the Go and Connect monthly newsletter you can easily change your email preferences when going to ‘My Profile’. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you will not be able to use several sections of the websites which require signing in, as the Service doesn’t recognize you as a member of Go and Connect. 

**Our Use of Your Information**  
The information acquired for the User Profile is only for the purpose of connecting Go and Connect network users in relation to specific postings on the individual websites. It is not sold, rented or made available to third parties. It may not be used to send Spam or third party advertisements to Go and Connect users. 

**Transmission and Security**  
Go and Connect is not responsible for problems resulting from or during connection to the site, including deletion, incomplete transmission or delays in sending information. Go and Connect is in compliance with all legal security measures regarding the protection of personal data supplied by the user. However, Go and Connect does not take responsibility for the possible breach of security regulations when caused by a third party using illegal measures or technologies, since it is impossible to guarantee the complete invulnerability of the system. 

**Control of Your Password**  
If you wish to change your password you can do so at any time through the ´My Profile´section, with the ´Change Password´ button at the top of the page. If you forget your password, just click on the button below to have it sent to you: http://www.barcelonaconnect.com/ForgotPassword.asp?pid=1238 You may not disclose your password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you should immediately change your password by visiting ´My Profile´page on the Site. Reviewing and Change Your Personally Identifiable Information You can at any time review and change the information you submitted during registration by opening ´My Profile´ on the site, after logging in. You can at any time ask to see and have removed any information that we have stored about you. If you want to deactivate your user profile yourself, you can do so in the following way: -Go to My Profile, located at the top left hand side of the Home Page. -Select the option ´Delete My Profile´that is situated at the bottom right of the page. 

**Links**  
Go and Connect provides links to other websites and third party property for information purposes only and cannot be held responsible for the content or services offered by said companies or organisations nor for the possible national and international legislation that said sites are obliged to comply with. 

**Legal Competence**  
Go and Connect and any Go and Connect user remain under the jurisdiction of Spanish legislation as the governing competence for this agreement and submit to the Courts and Tribunals of Barcelona for the resolution of any and all litigation that might arise from said agreement. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
Go and Connect reserves the right to modify this policy, in accordance with Spanish laws, and any changes will automatically appear on this page within thirty days. In the event of the merging or acquisition of Go and Connect, user information or any part of it will be disclosed to the new company. However, the Privacy Policy as detailed above will remain intact. If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form on the Contact Us section. 

Thank you. 

****Refund Policy** **

Due to the fact that magazine adverts can not be modified once they have been submitted for publication, or once they have been uploaded to the website, GO and Connect does not offer the possibility of refunds. If the Go and Connect team believes that the advert content is inappropriate for the magazine or website, the full amount of money will be refunded to the client before being submitted for publication on the web or in the magazine. All Go and Connect readers have the option of receiving a yearly subscription to the Go and Connect magazine for a small fee. Once a payment has been made by credit card or bank-transfer, a subscriber can decide tot cancel their subscription and the full amount will be refunded. After the seven day period has expired the subscription can not be cancelled. No refunds will be offered for temporary or permanent loss of Service howsoever arising, including but not limited to a loss of Service due to the Go and Connect website being unavailable for whatever reason. Go and Connect does not take any responsibility for monetary transactions at all.
